We'll be right back.
Find a way out.
Rocketman takes flight.
What a fantastic feeling.
It's so unfortunate.
The rest of the world may never know what a glorious accomplishment CP9 achieved today.
What are the drawbacks of being a secret agency and all that?
Yes, a pity.
Honestly, the news of your capture could take years to reach the public.
The justice those old geezers in the current world government dole out is far too lenient.
Without sacrifice, goals cannot be achieved.
I mean, this is world peace we're working for.
It's not easy.
Surely there can't be an issue with sacrificing a few fools along the way who hinder our work for the sake of the greater good.
Right.
You know, if everyone would just give us what we ask for obediently and without question, then we wouldn't have to go to such extreme measures like we had to with poor Tom.
That traitor deserved it.
Crazy bastard.
Tom put his life on the line to protect those blueprints.
Because idiots like you exist!
What are you doing?
Don't you sit there healthy.
Help me!
Kumonori!
Yoyoy!
What is your desire?
This isn't obvious how bigs make him stop!
So, so, so!
Yoyoy!
No need to bake me tea.
No need!
Yes!
Now come, come!
Ja!
Paul puru!
Naha!
Kom-kom-wak!
Giant sessar!
Kill!
Kibler!
CYI?!
This is Main Island calling the chief! Spondum, come in! I repeat, come in! It's no good, no signal!
Is that so? Maybe he's got the receiver off again.
Oh, seriously? Could his timing be any worse?
Hey! Anyone see where Straw Hat went?
He's right beneath you! What? He is?
Everyone attack him from all sides, now!
There he is! We got him!
Damn! I'm cornered!
Now, Gom-Gom!
Botana!
Ah!
What? No way! The walls are falling!
Now, Gom-Gom!
Gatling!
Ah!
Oh, no!
Chief Spondum, please come in.
We need your orders, sir.
We can't stop Straw Hat Luffy.
Get ready.
He's heading towards the courthouse.
We need those defenses lined up.
Move it, men.
Shut up already.
What's with all the yelling?
Ah, you guys booked me up.
Ah, Chief Justice.
Yep, you got it.
That's me, Chief Justice,
up in his lobby, on the left.
My name is Left Baskerville.
On the right, I am Right Baskerville.
And located in the center,
I am known as Central Freeway.
Say what?
Ah, Chief Justice, we've got a problem.
There's a pirate on a rampage on the main island, sir,
but we can't get in touch with Chief Spondum
to get an update on our orders.
Please, sir, take command on his behalf.
A pirate, you say?
All pirates are guilty.
Hmm.
There hasn't been a trial yet.
Even so, I think he's innocent.
Hmm.
Then I'll be neutral.
Yeah!
Say what?
Chief Justice, there's trouble, sir.
I just received a report.
The Straw Hat's accomplices have taken out Kashi
at the front gate.
Oimo's still fighting, but won't last much longer.
Say what?
That gate must not be breached.
Send 100 watchdogs to that location immediately, sir!
We're in trouble.
Our five-minute window is up.
Damn.
Hurry!
We've got to get the gate open for Rocket Man!
I will never let you do.
Okay, guys, we've picked the gate floor.
All you have to do now is push it open.
What?
Oh, crap!
Nice work!
You heard her!
Move it!
You stay away from that gate!
Go back, son!
Top knot!
Whoa!
Those galley-law foremen are incredible!
You think this puni rope is going to hold me?
Frankie family!
Pull!
Yeah!
No problem!
Gamora!
Sodom!
Grab that rope!
Oh, and Frankie family!
Don't stop until the gate is wide open!
Wait, wait, wait!
Hold on!
Slow down!
I'm getting dizzy!
Push the gate!
No!
Impossible!
The gates are opening!
What the hell is Oimo doing?
Umaar!
That reached the gate!
Let's go.
Oh, hey, hey!
There's no way. Is that a sea train?
What's going on here?
It is! Look at it! A sea train!
And it's not the Puffington.
It's another one, and it's headed this way at full speed!
They're crazy!
What are they trying to do, jump the fence?
Hurry! Close the gate! We can't let them through!
Come on! Get those doors shut!
Hey, Granny!
Yeah? What is it?
There's been a change of plans. I need you to give me as much speed as you got, okay?
Roger, please. Roger!
It seems we've had to switch up our plans a little. Your green-haired samurai friend says you should all find something to hold on to. Better hurry!
Find something to hold on to?
But why?
Hey, Mosfer Brains! What's going on out here?
They, uh, they closed the main gate.
Hey, what?
This is bad! We're gonna crash!
What are we gonna do? What are we gonna do?
Dodge it! Go to roll!
I've got a plan. Don't worry.
All right, Zoro!
Hey, Frogs! See fence? Smash!
What?
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Fire!
Get out! Get out!
This is planned? Does he realize what's gonna happen when we run into that fence?
Impossible!
That sea train!
It's flying!
No, no!
We're gonna die!
What?
But I don't want to die!
Maybe this way I'll save you! Fall into my arms!
Shut up, you idiot! I've got enough problems right now!
Zorro, you better have felt long and hard about how you're gonna land this thing!
Of course I have.
Ah!
We fall.
Get out!
I hate you!
We'll find out if luck's on our side soon enough!
Ah! Almost going down!
Agh!
Argh!
Ow.
I hate you!
I hate you, Logan!
We'll be right back.
So, our idiot captain rushed off by himself again, huh?
Well, we're the ones following that idiot around, so what does that make us?
Then again, thanks to Luffy, the marine forces are scattered all over the island.
Good. More for me. I'm not gonna let Luffy have all the fun.
On the next, One Piece, catch up with Luffy, the Straw Hat's all-out battle.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!